Ting Han Gan - Computer Science Student specialised in Data Science

https://tinghangan.github.io/portfolio/

Hard-working computer science student majoring in Data Science, with 3+ years of proven interpersonal and organisation skills of customer service in high intensity environments.

Seeking to contribute to a challenging workplace as a data analyst that strives in innovation to broaden knowledge and aim to help achieve company goals. Bilingual in English and Mandarin.



tinghan68@gmail.com

0478-839-328

linkedin.com/in/ting-han-gan/



github.com/TingHanGan

TECHNICAL (IT) SKILLS

Data Management Data Analysis, Pattern & Trend Identification, Visualisation of Data Insights, Creation of clean

reports using R Markdown & PDFs

Computer Science Proficient with R, Rscript, Python, Juypter Notebook, Tableau, Java, Troubleshooting

Experience in MySQL, Excel, Javascript, HTML/CSS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tsuru Japanese Restaurant, Melbourne VIC — Part Time

JANUARY 2021 - CURRENT

- Gained the trust to supervise and conduct staff training.
- Liaised between both kitchens and staff to ensure quality customer service is met.
- Managed reservations and stock count of drinks daily.

Crystal Palace Catering, Melbourne VIC — *Part Time*

JANUARY 2019 - JANUARY 2021

- Worked as an effective team member and leader to take orders and serve food in a range of diverse teams.
- Learnt the ability to balance workloads efficiently in a constantly changing and high intensity environment.
- Checked in with guests to uphold the company values of excellent customer service.

EDUCATION

Monash University, Clayton VIC

JANUARY 2019 - CURRENT

Bachelor of Computer Science

Major in Data Science; Minors in Business Information Systems and Korean

McKinnon Secondary College, McKinnon VIC – Victorian Certificate of Education (VCE)

JANUARY 2013 - DECEMBER 2018

Graduated at VCE Level

UNIVERSITY PROJECT

Covid-19 Data Collection and Tracing Application

JANUARY 2021 - CURRENT

- Led a group of students for the project as a Scrum master with data management tools, to ensure we are on track.
- Built multiple live interactive Tableau dashboards (e.g., Daily updates) connected to Google Sheets as a server to visualise relevant statistics of Covid-19, saving 3 hours a day of manual updating.
- Analysed data from 15+ sources to perform data analysis and present it in the form of Tableau dashboards and R Graphs.
- Utilised and created a website to store our data analysis findings and corresponding reports.

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Accenture, Virtual Internship Experience Program 2021 – 5 Hours

Participated in the open access Accenture Virtual Experience Program with Forage

Tasks Completed include:

- Identified crucial priorities for the project plan for client.
- Reviewed multiple sources and interpret, extract, and combine data through performing data analysis.
- Understood and identified Key Performance Indicators (KPI).

IT/CS Peer Mentor, Clayton VIC - Volunteer

JANUARY 2020 – JUNE 2020

- Assisted first years with any questions they had by planning information and social events.
- Ensured the smooth transition from high school to university for mentees.
- Developed necessary planning and leadership skills.